Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Clark, Hall and Peck, 1890s-1982; Series II
  - Index card file of the names of owners for all Clark, Hall & Peck title searches in all towns and cities
    - Lebov - Lonergan (Box 2177)
    - Lonetti - Maccio (Box 2178)
    - MacClemmy - Mango (Box 2179)
    - Mangs - Mascola (Box 2180)
    - Mascolo - McCuddy (Box 2181)
    - McCue - Meany (Box 2182)
    - Mear - Milford (Box 2183)
    - Milgreen - Montano (Box 2184)
    - Montauti - Mullen (Box 2185)
    - Muller - Neuse (Box 2186)
    - Neuweiler - Nystrom (Box 2187)
    - O. F. Mossberg & Sons Inc. - Orser (Box 2188)
    - Orsi - Paramount Roll Thread Co. (Box 2189)
    - Paraskeva - Pendlebury (Box 2190)
    - Pendleton - Piascyk (Box 2191)
    - Piasecki - Portnoy (Box 2192)
    - Porto - Rabuano (Box 2193)
    - Racca - Reinhold (Box 2194)
    - Reinholtz - Rivazzi (Box 2195)
    - Rivino - Rosenthal (Box 2196)
    - Rosenvik - Ryalls (Box 2197)
    - Ryan - Sarris (Box 2198)
    - Sarro - Schulman (Box 2199)
    - Schulte - Shavitz (Box 2200)
    - Shaw - Simons (Box 2201)
    - Simos - Smiy (Box 2202)
    - Smoko - Stankowitz (Box 2203)
    - Stanley - Sulkowitch (Box 2204)
    - Sullivan - Tavoliero (Box 2205)
    - Taylor - Tirpak (Box 2206)
    - Tirrell - Turcott (Box 2207)
    - Turczaniewicz - Velardy (Box 2208)
    - Velimirovic - Walkowsky (Box 2209)
    - Wall - Weitzel (Box 2210)
    - Welbourne - William (Box 2211)
    - Williams - Wright, Marilyn (Box 2212)
    - Wright, Nellie - Zywocinski (Box 2213)
    - Probate
      - Index card files of last names
        - Aaronson - Buonocore (Box 2214)
        - Burchard - Dziadik (Box 2215)
        - Eagan - Hills (Box 2216)
        - Hinckley - Mannix (Box 2217)
        - Manser - Pitkin (Box 2218)
        - Plant - Starr (Box 2219)
        - Stebbins - Zwick (Box 2220)
      - Probate files
        - Abbott - Barstow (Box 2221)
        - Bartholomew - Bradbury (Box 2222)
        - Bradley - Byrnes (Box 2223)
        - Cable - Converse (Box 2224)
        - Conway - Dore (Box 2225)
        - Dorman - Foote (Box 2226)
        - Forbes - Grannis (Box 2227)
        - Grant - Hooker (Box 2228)
        - Hope - Judson (Box 2229)
        - Kain - Lind (Box 2230)
        - Lindsley - Mead (Box 2231)
        - Meehan - Myers (Box 2232)
        - Naclerio - Phipps (Box 2233)
        - Pierre - Rosoff (Box 2234)
        - Ross - Smedley (Box 2235)
        - Smith - Thompson, Ch. (Box 2236)
        - Thompson, Cl. - Wallace (Box 2237)
        - Walsh - Zurber (Box 2238)
  - Index card file (unidentified)
    The unidentified index to abstracts and flat files is arranged alphabetically by property owner or property name. It does not index or contain references to addresses.
    - A-H (Box 2375)
    - I-R (Box 2376)
    - S-Y (Box 2377)
- Indices, atlases, and maps, 1860s-1950s; Series III
  This series is arranged by type of material.
  This series contains indices, atlases, and maps that White Brothers and Clark, Hall and Peck maintained to assist them in performing title searches. Both the handwritten and typed indicies were superseded by the index card filing system and do not have much current utility. The atlases and maps range from 1888 to the middle of the twentieth century and are of historical value since some depict detailed information about the built environment and land ownership patterns.
  Handwritten and typed indices for abstracts of title appear first. They are generally arranged by city or town, and list each owner and a description of the property along with locator information such as an abstract number. This was superseded by the index card system.
  The New Haven land record and conveyance indices are brief summaries prepared by Clark, Hall, and Peck of land records found in the New Haven city clerk's office. Every entry lists the volume and page number where the particular document is found in the clerk's office, the names of the seller and buyer, the type of conveyance (warranty deed, lease, mortgage, etc.), and a description of the property. These volumes are incomplete and are of little value for accessing the records in the Clark, Hall, and Peck series.
  The handwritten probate index is an alphabetical listing of Clark, Hall and Peck's probate records which was superseded by the index card file of last names.
  The map books in the collection all belonged to the firm of Clark, Hall and Peck. Of most interest to the researcher will be the New Haven Atlas, which shows the district system used by the law firm; and the tax assessment volumes for Fair Haven, Westville, and West Haven. These last three volumes contain detailed area maps showing property and building lines.
  Other map books in the collection are of historical interest. The 1911 Atlas of New Haven, Connecticut contains maps that detail the city's layout and property owners. Maps, Volumes 1, 2, and 3, contain a combination of manuscript and printed maps, some of which are handcolored. They date from the 1860s and 1870s through the mid-portion of the twentieth century. The maps detail housing developments; lots for sale and auction in New Haven; different areas of the city, and the surrounding towns; and notable properties, such as mansions, farms, and factories. An untitled 500 page folio volume contains manuscripts sketches of various areas of New Haven, and handwritten notes regarding property ownership.
  Individual maps used by both law firms are found at the end of Series III.
  - Indices
    - Abstracts of title
      - New Haven (Box 2239)
        Handwritten index.
      - New Haven (Box 2240)
        Typewritten index, also includes the records for Annex 1-387, Westville 2097-3223, Ansonia 1-142, Bethany 1-792, Branford 1-2443, Milford 1083-6669.
      - Annex 1 – Annex 4 (Books 1-2) (Box 2241)
      - Westville (1-2096) (Box 2242)
      - Other towns (Box 2243)
        Handwritten index for records from Ansonia, Beacon Falls, Bethany, Branford, Cheshire, Clinton, Derby, Guilford, Madison, Meriden, Middlebury, Naugatuck, New Milford, North Branford, North Haven, Norwich, Prospect, Seymour, Union City, Wallingford, Waterbury, Wolcott, and Woodbridge.
      - Other towns (Box 2244)
        Typewritten index for records from Bridgeport, Bristol, Burlington, Cheshire, Clinton, Coventry, Cromwell, Danbury, Deep River, Derby, Durham, East Lyme, Easton, Enfield, Essex, Fairfield, Greenwich, Groton, Guilford, Hartford, Killingworth, Litchfield, Lyme, Madison, Manchester, Meriden, Middlebury, Middletown, Monroe, Montville, Naugatuck, New Britain, New Canaan, New Hartford, New London, New Milford, Newington, Newtown, Norfolk, North Branford, Norwalk, Norwich, Old Lyme, Old Saybrook, Oxford, Plainville, Prospect, Ridgefield, Salisbury, Salem, Saybrook, Seymour, Sharon, Shelton, Southbury, Southington, Stamford, Sterling, Stratford, Thomaston, Thompson, Trumbull, Wallingford, Waterbury, Westbrook, Weston, Wolcott, and Woodbury.
      - East Haven (1-1566) (Box 2245)
      - East Haven (1567-4294) (Box 2246)
        Typewritten index, also contains records for Hamden 4304-10528, North Haven 1-4268, Woodbridge 1-1681.
      - Hamden (1-4303) (Box 2247)
      - Milford (1-1082) (Box 2248)
      - West Haven (West Haven districts 1-14, "West Haven," and Orange), 2 (Box 2249)
    - New Haven land records and conveyances
      - Grantee index (Last names A-B) (Box 2250)
      - Index to New Haven Land Records Volumes 541-550 (Last names A-Z) (Box 2251)
      - New Haven conveyance records index (Abbe – Bon) (Box 2252)
      - New Haven conveyance records index (Boom - Clark, Norton) (Box 2253)
      - New Haven conveyance records index (Clark, Norton - Dwight, Timothy) (Box 2254)
      - New Haven conveyance records index (Dwight, Timothy – Fellows, Alvin J.) (Box 2255)
    - Probate Index (Last names A-Z) (Box 2256)
      Superseded by index card system in 1965.
  - Map books
    - New Haven
      - Atlas, 1888 (Box 2257)
        Atlas of City of New Haven from records from Engineering Department published by G. M. Hopkins, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      - Annex, Circa 1886-1897 (Box 2258)
        CHP map book of the Annex; Annexed District of Town of New Haven, Bogart & Sperry, Eng.
      - Westville (CHP map book of Westville) (Box 2259)
      - Other New Haven map books
        - Atlas of New Haven, Connecticut, 1911 (Box 2260)
          Compiled by Streuli & Puckhafer, Eng., copyright Oscar W. Walker and Streuli & Puckhafer, Boston, Massachusetts.
        - "Maps Vol. 1", Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 2261)
          Undated volume consisting of lithographed maps, handdrawn maps and sketches of property in New Haven County.
        - "Maps Vol. 2", Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 2262)
        - "Maps Vol. 3", Undated (Box 2263)
        - Untitled volume (Box 2264)
          Manuscript sketches of areas of New Haven County.
        - Untitled volume (Fair Haven maps) (Box 2265)
          Consists of a fairly complete set of tax maps #100-139 with lot dimensions, building outlines and some numbering of lots, states "corrected to 1913".
        - Untitled volume (Westville maps) (Box 2266)
          Consists of a set of tax assessment maps in with lot dimensions and building outlines.
    - Other cities and towns
      - Atlas of New Haven County, Connecticut, 1860 (Box 2267)
        Includes business directory and atlas.
      - West Haven (CHP map book of West Haven) (Box 2268)
        Consists of a bound set of approximately 36 undated tax assessment maps by C. H. Nichols, Eng., in blueprint color with lot dimensions and building outlines.
  - Maps of New Haven
    - Map of New Haven and Suburbs, 1922 August 15 (Folder 2269a)
      Wall map of city (White Brothers New Haven district map).
      - Digital use copy
      - Use copy (Box 2269)
    - Clark, Hall and Peck maps
      Consists of eighty double sided mounted maps on vertical panels of various areas of the city with notations concerning properties.
      Map 97 and 98 was missing when the records were received from the donor.
      There is no Map 12, Map 97, Map 98, Map 146, Map 149, Map 150, Map 159, Map 160, Map 161.
      - Map 1 and 2 (Box 2270)
      - Map 3 and 4 (Box 2271)
      - Map 5 and 6 (Box 2272)
      - Map 7 and 8 (Box 2273)
      - Map 9 and 10 (Box 2274)
      - Map 11 (Box 2275)
      - Map 13 and 14 (Box 2276)
      - Map 15 and 16 (Box 2277)
      - Map 17 and 18 (Box 2278)
      - Map 19 and 20 (Box 2279)
      - Map 21 and 22 (Box 2280)
      - Map 23 and 24 (Box 2281)
      - Map 25 and 26 (Box 2282)
      - Map 27 and 28 (Box 2283)
      - Map 29 and 30 (Box 2284)
      - Map 31 and 32 (Box 2285)
      - Map 33 and 34 (Box 2286)
      - Map 35 and 36 (Box 2287)
      - Map 37 and 38 (Box 2288)
      - Map 39 and 40 (Box 2289)
      - Map 41 and 42 (Box 2290)
      - Map 43 and 44 (Box 2291)
      - Map 45 and 46 (Box 2292)
      - Map 47 and 48 (Box 2293)
      - Map 49 and 50 (Box 2294)
      - Map 51 and 52 (Box 2295)
      - Map 53 and 54 (Box 2296)
      - Map 55 and 56 (Box 2297)
      - Map 57 and 58 (Box 2298)
      - Map 59 and 60 (Box 2299)
      - Map 61 and 62 (Box 2300)
      - Map 63 and 64 (Box 2301)
      - Map 65 and 66 (Box 2302)
      - Map 67 and 68 (Box 2303)
      - Map 69 and 70 (Box 2304)
      - Map 71 and 72 (Box 2305)
      - Map 73 and 74 (Box 2306)
      - Map 75 and 76 (Box 2307)
      - Map 77 and 78 (Box 2308)
      - Map 79 and 80 (Box 2309)
      - Map 81 and 82 (Box 2310)
      - Map 83 and 84 (Box 2311)
      - Map 85 and 86 (Box 2312)
      - Map 87 and 88 (Box 2313)
      - Map 89 and 90 (Box 2314)
      - Map 91 and 92 (Box 2315)
      - Map 93 and 94 (Box 2316)
      - Map 95 and 96 (Box 2317)
      - Map 99 and 100 (Box 2318)
      - Map 101 and 102 (Box 2319)
      - Map 103 and 104 (Box 2320)
      - Map 105 and 106 (Box 2321)
      - Map 107 and 108 (Box 2322)
      - Map 109 and 110 (Box 2323)
      - Map 111 and 112 (Box 2324)
      - Map 113 and 114 (Box 2325)
      - Map 115 and 116 (Box 2326)
      - Map 117 and 118 (Box 2327)
      - Map 119 and 120 (Box 2328)
      - Map 121 and 122 (Box 2329)
      - Map 123 and 124 (Box 2362)
      - Map 125 and 126 (Box 2330)
      - Map 127 and 128 (Box 2331)
      - Map 129 and 130 (Box 2332)
      - Map 131 and 132 (Box 2333)
      - Map 133 and 134 (Box 2334)
      - Map 135 and 136 (Box 2335)
      - Map 137 and 138 (Box 2336)
      - Map 139 and 140 (Box 2337)
      - Map 141 and 143 (Box 2338)
        Map 141 is also labeled Westville Number 1.
      - Map 144 and 145A (Box 2339)
      - Map 145B and 145C (Box 2340)
      - Map 145D (Box 2341)
      - Map 147 and 148 (Box 2342)
      - Map 151A and 152 (Box 2343)
      - Map 151B (Box 2344)
      - Map 153 and 154 (Box 2345)
      - Map 155 and 156 (Box 2346)
      - Map 157 and 158 (Box 2347)
      - Map 162 (Box 2348)
      - Map 163 and 164 (Box 2349)
      - Map 164 (old) and 165 (Box 2350)
      - Map 166A and 166B (Box 2351)
      - Map 167A and 167B (Box 2352)
      - Map 168A and 168B (Box 2353)
      - Map 168C and 169B (Box 2354)
      - Map 168D and 169B (Box 2355)
      - Map 171A and 172A (Box 2356)
      - Map 172B and 172C (Box 2357)
      - Map 173A and 173B (Box 2358)
      - Map 174A and 174C (Box 2359)
      - Map 173C and 174B (Box 2360)
      - Map 175A and 175B (Box 2361)
      - West Haven Map 36 and 37 (Box 2363)
      - West Haven Map 38 and 39 (Box 2364)
      - West Haven Map 40 and 41 (Box 2365)
      - West Haven Map 42 and 43 (Box 2366)
      - West Haven Map 44 and 45 (Box 2367)
      - West Haven Map 46 and 47 (Box 2368)
      - West Haven Map 48 and 49 (Box 2369)
      - West Haven Map 50 and 51 (Box 2370)
      - West Haven Map 52 and 53 (Box 2371)
      - West Haven Map 55 (Box 2372)
      - West Haven Map 56 (Box 2373)
      - West Haven Map 58 and 59 (Box 2374)